seek.uk.com 2008-09-12

# Privacy Policy of seek.uk.com

Privacy Policy - Rupiz media 

The concept of privacy holds a paramount place in today's scenario henceforth; the Company envisages certain privacy policy, so that the personal and other information of the users can be preserved. The Company endeavours to take all efforts which are required for maintaining online privacy norms on up-to-date basis which shows you the way towards safe and secured transactions. In order to understand how you provide information to us, and how the information collected is used by us, we request that all affiliates and merchants/advertisers read this policy.

This privacy policy applies to the global operations of Rupiz media including its operations in Europe. We are registered under Data Protection Act, 1998, No: Z9658904

**We are registered under Data Protection Act, 1998, DPR No: Z9657804.**

**1\. Purpose of this policy**

The purpose of this policy is:

> • to assure you that we recognise and fully respect the privacy and personal data of the visitors to this website and   
>  • to explain what personal information we collect from this website and how we ensure its' best protection.

By your access to and use of this website you agree to our processing, storing and using those information in accordance with the principles set out in this Privacy Policy.

**2\. Collection of Information**

We collect personal information when you register yourself as a Merchant or an Affiliate or you have applied to become as a registered Merchant or Affiliate or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. We may use cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use our websites in order to improve the quality of our websites.

We will limit the collection and use of your information to a minimum. We require and collect relevant program information, including but not limited to log-in, contact, company, website, website user and payment data in order to manage your account and provide you with the services requested. In addition once you become our member, we require sales and earnings data, and we collect performance statistics related to your affiliate program(s) in order to properly compensate our users.

Information is collected by us but is the sole property of the advertiser and is shared only with the advertiser.

The information you provide may also be used for analytical and statistical purposes.

**3\. Uses of Information**

We may use the information to provide the products you've requested. We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our technologies and websites.

We may use the information to inform you about any changes in the terms and conditions, provide you with access to any services that you may chose to subscribe to, contact you when reasonably necessary and to communicate with you about your use of the Services any changes to the Services. We may use the information to send you promotional email messages including newsletters which we believe will be interesting or useful to you, but only if you have agreed to allow us to send these messages to you. We may also use and share your personal information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and websites.

We may also use any information you have entered into the website as reasonably necessary to provide customer support for the website and our products and services.

4\. Disclosure of Information

We do not share, sell or rent your e-mail, postal address, or any other data we hold about you to any third party, unless a prior consent is obtained from you. We may however disclose your personal information as and when required under law, in cases where it is obligatory to do so. In order to help our registered merchants and affiliates to make educated decisions while forming affiliations, we share specific information with them. Merchants and affiliates may contact each other to solicit affiliation or who are considering forming an affiliation. They may view pertinent company, contact, performance information and additional details.

We do not share or sell your data to unaffiliated third parties. 

We may share sales and performance information necessary to calculate commission payments from merchants to affiliates after an affiliation has been formed.

For the purpose of educating potential merchants and affiliates, from time to time, we may share non-user specific, aggregate information, or company names. No personal identifying information will be included in such information and your identity will remain absolutely anonymous.

We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and amend it, when reasonably possible.

**5\. Security of Information**

We will take all reasonable steps to safeguard the security and confidentiality of any information you provide to us. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) Encryption, to make sure that all information is secure. Secure Sockets Layer technology secures our Web site by encrypting information and providing authentication. We cannot, however, guarantee the security of any information you disclose online. You accept the inherent security implications of providing information over the Internet and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security or disclosure of information unless we have been negligent. Your personal information will be preserved within the Company or on its behalf wherever it is mandatory to do so and for this purpose adequate steps will be pursued to shield the personal information from unlawful access.

**6\. Access to collected information**

We provide site members, merchants and affiliates with access to all information that we maintain about them, including unique identifier, transaction and contact information upon proper verification. The same can be provided to you on request, in case the members experience any doubts.

**7\. Cookies**

To facilitate your use of our website and to collect aggregate information, we may use “cookies”. Cookies are merely text files, used to identify individual users. They are placed in computer's browser to store preferences. Cookies, are not plug ins nor are they programs. They are stored on the computer's hard drive and can be deleted at any time. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser.

Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us email address or other personal information unless a person choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our site. They do not contain any personal information about you. Cookies do not act maliciously on computer systems.

To view our Cookie Policy, please click here. 

**8\. Changes to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to revise this policy at any time. If this privacy policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with others.

**9\. Consent**

We are not responsible for the privacy policies of our partner merchants' and affiliates' sites and advise you to familiarize yourself with their respective policies. By using this website you consent to the collection and use of your personal information in the manner set out above.

**10\. More Information**

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of the Company or require any further information please send your request by email to legal@rupizmedia.com
